# PROFILE

A creative maverick having 5+ experience in creative world. Able to visualise, create effective and innovative designs to convey desired idea. Experience working with clients to identify needs and present solutions. Collaborating with marketing, sales and product development departments. Flexible problemsolver able to adapt to changing circumstances and needs.



## CONTACT

amreshkannal@gmail.com

## PORTFOLIO

Bē

https://www.behance.net/amreshkanna

TOOLS & SKILLS

## ABILITIES

+91 9700-989-588



Logo & Branding



Print Designs



Photography



Video Editing











# EDUCATION

#### **KITSW**

Graduation - Bachelors in
O Information Technology
Jul 2013 - May 2016

India

### **VMR POLYTECHNIC COLLEGE**

O Diploma - DEEE Engg Jul 2010 - May 2013 India

## INTERESTS







## WORK EXPERIENCE

#### **FREELANCING**

Oct 2020 - Present

**INDIAN SCHOOL OF BUSINESS, HYD** 

Feb 2020 - Oct 2020

Design Specialist

Worked on Marketing collaterals like logos, banners, posters, social media post, flyers, brochures and other designs.

PACTERA EDGE TECHNOLOGIES LTD, HYD

′ Jan 2019 - Jan 2020

Graphic Designer

Worked on Marketing collaterals like logos, banners, posters, social media post, flyers, brochures and Business presentations for B2B ,B2C, Sales decks.

**SVAPPS SOFT SOLUTIONS PVT LTD, WGL** 

UI

JUL 2016 - Aug 2018

**Developer** 

Worked on Marketing collaterals like logos, banners, posters, social media post, flyers, brochures and Website Front part.